https://www.salsa-dvds.com/conditions-of-use

Steps4Salsa
Your Currency:
Gregrory Campillo & Jessica Diaz
Fabrizio (Fabsalseros)
SalsaCrazy
SalsAddiction (Brian & Mechteld)
Yoannis Tamayo
Yvonne Laycy (form Goldsmith)
/
Conditions of Use for Salsa-DVDs.com, your shop for Latin & Salsa Instruction and Show DVD s
Search
Go
Conditions of Use
Acceptance of Terms, Agreement.
1. Steps4Salsa, Salsa-dvds.com and Salsa-videos.com are divisions of Steps4Dance. Please read these Terms and Conditions and our Privacy Policy carefully before accessing or using the Salsa-videos.com or Steps4salsa.com Web Site (the "Site"). By using the Site, you agree to be bound by all of the terms and conditions stated herein and to comply with our Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to be bound by these terms and conditions, you may not access or use the Site. Steps4Dance may revise these terms and conditions or the Privacy Policy at any time without notice and such modifications shall be deemed effective immediately upon posting of the modified terms and conditions or Privacy Policy, as the case may be. You agree to review the terms and conditions and the Privacy Policy periodically to be aware of such modifications and your continued access or use of the Site shall be deemed conclusive acceptance by you of the modified terms and conditions or Privacy Policy, as the case may be. If any changes or modifications to the terms and conditions or Privacy Policy are unacceptable to you, you may terminate your use of the Site.
2. Steps4Dance Privacy Policy. Information that we collect about you is subject to our Privacy Policy. For more information, please see our full privacy policy. By using the Site and providing information about yourself, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to our Privacy Policy.
3. No Resale. You agree not to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, resell or exploit for any commercial purposes, any portion of the Site, use of the Site or access to the Site.
4. Modifications to Site. Steps4Dance reserves the right at any time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Site (or any part thereof) with or without notice. You agree that Steps4Dance shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the Site.
5. Relationships with Advertisers and Other Marketing Persons or Entities. You understand that, to the extent that you have correspondence or business dealings or that you participate in the promotions of ("Marketing Dealings") advertisers or other marketing persons or entities found on or through the Site, such Marketing Dealings, including payment and delivery of the related goods or services, and any other terms, conditions, warranties or representations associated with such dealings, are solely between you and such advertiser or marketing persons or entity. You agree that Salsa-videos.com shall not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as the result of any such dealings or as the result of the presence of such advertisers or marketing persons or entities on the Site.
6. Steps4Dance's Proprietary Rights. You acknowledge and agree that the Site contains proprietary and confidential information that is protected by applicable intellectual property and other laws. You further acknowledge and agree that Content contained in sponsor advertisements or information presented to you through the Site or advertisers is protected by copyright, trademarks, service marks, patents or other proprietary rights and laws. Except as expressly authorized by Salsa-videos.com or advertisers, you agree not to modify, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute or create derivative works based on the Site, in whole or in part.
7. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES. YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT, EXCEPT TO THE EXTENT THAT YOUR JURISDICTION OTHERWISE PROHIBITS SUCH LIMITATIONS: a. YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE SITE IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. SALSA-VIDEOS.COM EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON INFRINGEMENT. b. Steps4Dance MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT (I) THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS; (II) THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECUIRE OR ERROR-FREE; (III) THE QUALITY OF ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, INFORMATION OR OTHER MATERIAL PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS; AND (IV) ANY ERRORS IN THE SITE WILL BE CORRECTED. c. ANY MATERIAL THAT YOU DOWNLOAD OR OTHERWISE OBTAIN THROUGH THE USE OF THE SITE IS DONE SO AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK. Steps4Dance ASSUMES NO LIABILITY WITH RESPECT TO SUCH MATERIAL AND YOU ARE AND WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIAL. d. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED FROM Steps4Dance OR THROUGH OR FROM THE SITE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY STATED IN THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS.
8. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT, EXCEPT TO THE EXTENT THAT YOUR JURISDICTION OTHERWISE PROHIBITS SUCH LIMITATIONS, Steps4Dance SHALL HAVE NO LIABILITY FOR DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, USE, DATA OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES (EVEN IF Steps4Dance HAS BEEN NOTIFIED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES), RESULTING FROM (I) USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE; (II) THE COST OF PROCURING SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES FOR ANY GOODS, DATA, INFORMATION OR SERVICES PURCHASED OR OBTAINED OR ANY MESSAGES RECEIVED OR ANY TRANSACTIONS ENTERED INTO THROUGH OR FROM THE SITE; (III) ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF YOUR DATA TRANSMISSIONS OR CONTENT; (IV) STATEMENTS OR CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTY ON THE SITE; OR (V) ANY OTHER MATTER RELATING TO THE SITE.
9. Notice. Notices to you may be made via email messages from Steps4Dance or regular mail.
10. Trademark Information. You acknowledge and agree that the Salsa-videos.com, steps4salsa and other Steps4Dance logos, products and service names are trademarks of Salsa-videos.com ("Salsa-videos.com Marks") or Steps4salsa ("Steps4salsa Marks") and you agree that you will not display or use the Salsa-videos.com Marks or Steps4Salsa Marks in any manner, without the express written permission of Steps4Dance.
11. Copyrights and Copyright Agents. If you believe that the Site contain material that constitutes an infringement of your copyright in any work, please provide the following information to our web site manager: a. a description of the copyrighted work that you claim is infringed; b. a description of where, in the Site, you claim that the copyright is infringed; c. a statement by that that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law; d. your address, telephone number and email address; e. an electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest; f. a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or are authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner. The Salsa-videos.com web site manager can be reached at info@Salsa-videos.com or info@Steps4dance.com
12. All sales are final. After placing your order you have the right to cancel it within seven business days. If for any reason a product is not in stock at the time of your order, we will notify you as soon as possible, with the expected approximate date of delivery. If we are not able to ship the order within 30 days after the one week 'grace period', you have the right to cancel it and receive a full refund for that (part of your) order. Customer is liable for all charges made by customs entering the country of destination.
My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Follow us
Newsletter Sign-up:
© 2011 Steps4Salsa. All Rights Reserved.
